#### Contact

smppatel99999@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ smppatel99999 (LinkedIn) sahilpatel09.github.io/ (Portfolio)

### Languages

Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Full Professional)
English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Goldman Sachs Engineering Virtual Program Internship

JPMorgan Chase Software Engineering Virtual Experience

Deloitte STEM Connect Virtual Experience Program

# Sahil Patel

Front-end Web Developer | Vue.js | Node.js | Firebase | Supabase | Python | Mongo DB | PostgreSQL | Interested in starting a new position.

Montreal

## Summary

Ever since my childhood, I have been obsessed with technology. I remember learning HTML & CSS when I was 11 years old. Well, now that is not the case. I have come very far in learning and working in technology field. I have mostly worked freelance, and now trying to pave my way in the corporate.

My goal is to use my knowledge and skills for the betterment of humanity. I dream to be in a crucial core part of a big MNC wherein I can use all of my skills and expertise to help the organization grow.

:

- · Quickly learning new skills and programming languages.
- Problem Solving.
- · Multitasking.
- So far, I have Java & Kotlin, HTML, CSS, SQL & PostgreSQL, JavaScript, and Python in my arsenal of tools.
- Academic qualifications such as Data Structures and Algorithm,
   Problem Solving, Operating System, Database Management
   Systems, Computer Networks, Software Engineering, and Project Management.

I am still enthusiastically grabbing onto any other skills or principles I can integrate into the coding web in my head.

Currently, I am spending my time in building open-source projects and upgrading my self as well promoting in the online world. I am interested in Web Development & Mobile Development related opportunities to kick-start my career in this vast field.

## Experience

Strotas Ayurherb Ind.

Frontend Web Developer April 2021 - January 2022 (10 months)

helped with e-commerce API development. Rewrote the Vue website in Nuxt. Helped designing web pages with Tailwind CSS. Deployed website to Netlify. Added support for Firebase to the E-commerce app.

iPratama Web Developer December 2019 - September 2020 (10 months) Montreal, Quebec, Canada

WordPress theme development and maintenance. Custom website development with front-end technologies, React and Vue js.

### Education

College Matrix

College Diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (May 2019 - December 2020)